Ouch.
好痛...
Na-Natsukawa?
夏...夏川
Wataru.
阿涉...
It hurts.
好痛喔...
Where are you rushing off to in such a hurry?
妳怎麼這麼匆忙啊？
It hurts.
(你身上有汗味... 看來你很勤奮嘛) 好痛喔...
What are you doing?
你在幹嘛啊
Because I did a lot of manual labor today.
我今天做了很多粗重的工作嘛
-I saw it. -You saw it?
-我有看到 -妳看到了？
She's actually watching me?
夏川她居然看到我了
Did she know I was there?
原來她知道我在這裡嗎
No, when did she find out?
不對 她什麼時候發現的
Why didn't she greet me directly…
為什麼她不直接跟我打招呼...
Right, she wouldn't take the initiative to greet me.
也對 她不可能主動跟我打招呼
You smell like sweat.
你身上有汗味...
It looks like you've been doing a lot of work.
看來你很勤奮嘛
W-What's going on? What's happening?
這是...怎麼回事
This is the first time she's been this close to me!
她第一次靠我這麼近
Is she losing her sense of distance because she hasn't seen me in so long?
是因為我們太久沒見 讓她的距離感錯亂了嗎
-Na-Natsukawa. -What's up?
-夏川... -怎麼了嗎
Um…
那個…
Something good happen to you?
妳遇到什麼好事了嗎
No, how should I put it?
呃...該怎麼說呢
I feel like you're being very gentle today.
我覺得妳今天態度很溫和...
Because you're closer to me than usual.
因為妳平時不會這麼靠近我
Yes.
也是啦
She wouldn't intentionally get close to me.
夏川她怎麼可能會特意靠近我
I-I'm sorry.
抱...抱歉
-It's so hot. -S-She's really cute.
-好熱喔 -這...太可愛了吧
If I'm not careful, I'll find myself constantly praising her.
一個不小心 我就會忍不住想一直誇讚她了
So, what is it? Do you need something?
所以...妳有什麼事嗎
You seem to be in a hurry to get somewhere.
我看妳好像趕著去哪
Well, that's because… I…
那是因為...我...
I saw you…
我看到你...
I saw you, so I ran over.
我看到你就跑過來了
Me?
因為我？
Why would you run over when you saw me?
為什麼呢
Why?
你問我為什麼...
I'd like to ask you, too, why you didn't come to find me.
我才想問你為什麼不來找我呢
Why?
為什麼不找妳...
Because I thought it would be better not to bother you.
因為我覺得我不該去打擾妳
It's been so long since we've seen each other.
我們這麼久沒見面了...
D-Don't you miss me?
你就不會覺得寂寞嗎
You're too cute.
妳也太可愛了吧
What? Really!
什麼嘛 真是的
That's what's annoying about you.
你就是這點很討人厭
And that's exactly why people like you.
而妳就是這點讓人喜歡
It's my fault.
是我不好啦
Because I really didn't have time.
因為我實在沒空
I know.
我知道
You said it in the text message.
你傳訊息的時候有說
Indeed.
嗯 對喔
You said a lot happened at your part-time job.
你說你打工發生了很多事
Like the matter of Ichinose?
像是一之瀨同學的事
Yes, everything went smoothly after that.
沒錯 後來一切都很順利
Your advice encouraged me to pay closer attention to other people's problems.
多虧了妳的建議 才讓我好好地傾聽她的煩惱
Thank you.
謝謝妳
So you guys are getting along, huh?
你們...關係變好了是嗎
Yes, I guess so.
是啊 應該變好了
Although I can't say we're getting along very well,
雖然也不算是特別好
I do believe we're getting closer.
但我覺得我們變熟很多了
I see, that's good.
是喔...那就好
Yes, I'm really relieved.
是啊 我真是鬆了口氣
Huh? That's it?
咦 話題就結束了嗎
Is she not going to ask what happened after that?
她不問問我之後發生的事嗎
Isn't she curious?
她怎麼不會覺得好奇
Right, this is someone else's business after all.
不對 這畢竟是別人的家務事
Natsukawa is most likely polite, so she isn't asking too much, right?
夏川她應該是出於禮貌而不多過問吧
Anyway, she's probably not that interested in me.
反正她對我的事應該也沒什麼興趣
Speaking of which, it's been a long time since we last met.
話說回來 我們真是好久不見了
This should be the first time we've met since the summer vacation, right?
這應該是暑假後我們第一次見面吧
Is it? Did you get a tan?
對了 妳是不是有點曬黑了啊
Because I went to the beach with Kei.
我跟圭有去海邊玩...
Speaking of which, Ashida sent me a photo.
對喔 蘆田有傳照片來...
Y-Yes. That photo.
對...那時候的照片
Kei said she recalled the message, but you still received it, didn't you?
圭說她收回訊息了 結果你還是收到照片了嗎
I don't see what the problem is?
這沒什麼大不了的吧
Hey. Don't evade the question.
喂 你不要答非所問
Huh? What do you mean?
妳要幹嘛
Give me your phone.
把你的手機給我
Na-Natsukawa, this is a bit…
夏川...這有點...
Wataru, I…
阿涉...我問你
Huh? It's Aika indeed.
咦 果然是小愛啊
And Sajo.
還有小佐城
Kei.
圭
Oh my goodness, you just scared me.
唉呀 剛才妳真是嚇我一跳
You jumped on me.
妳幹嘛突然撲過來啦
S-Sorry, I just instinctively…
抱歉...我一不小心就...
It's okay. Rather, I'm happy.
沒關係 反正我很高興
Here you go, please drink this.
這給妳們喝吧
Thank you, Sajo.
小佐城謝謝你
Thank you.
謝謝
Do you have to attend club activities every day?
妳每天都要來練球嗎
It's not like I have to go every day.
是沒有每天啦
But the volleyball club has a lot of matches.
但排球隊有很多比賽嘛
Like the upcoming summer tournament and exchange match.
接下來就有夏季大賽跟交流賽之類的
Because you'll be a full-fledged player next year, Kei.
畢竟圭妳明年有望成為主力選手嘛
You seem very energetic.
妳可真是活力十足耶
Sajo, did you get tanned too?
小佐城你是不是也曬黑了啊
Well, because I went to White Beach--
嗯 我去了趟美白濱...
Because I go out to work every day.
因為...我每天都要出門打工嘛
Why are you panicking?
小佐城你那麼慌張幹嘛
I definitely didn't do anything guilty.
我絕對沒有做虧心事
That's exactly what a guilty person would say.
這不是做了虧心事的人才會說的話嗎
Damn. Why must you be so astute at this crucial juncture?
可惡 她為什麼偏偏這時候這麼敏銳
Do I have to say I played with a college-looking middle schooler?
難道我要說我跟一個 有如大學生的女國中生出去玩嗎
Absolutely not.
絕對不行
Why don't you sit down?
你先坐下吧
Come, sit here.
坐這裡
Sit there?
那裡？
You're not happy?
你不想嗎
Not really.
倒也不是
So why did you come to school today?
所以你今天怎麼會來學校啊
Right. I wanted to ask too.
對啊 我也想知道
I'm here because my sister asked me to.
是我老姊拜託我來的
She asked me to assist in decorating the campus open day venue.
她要我幫忙佈置校園參觀日的會場
Why did your sister ask you to help?
為什麼要找你啊
It's a long story.
這就說來話長了
It means your sister relies on you.
這表示你姊很信賴你嘛
No, she just treats me as a servant.
才沒有 她只是把我當僕人使喚
By the way, regarding the open day guide…
對了 參觀日那天的嚮導...
Ordinary people aren't usually given jobs like this, right?
這種工作一般不會讓普通人負責吧
Huh? What do you mean?
什麼意思啊
Senior Shinomiya…
四之宮學姊她...
She had previously told me, somewhat awkwardly,
她之前有點尷尬地跟我說
that the school had specifically selected high-spec people
學校為了吸引更多學生入學
to be guides in order to attract more students.
會特地挑選高規格的學生來擔任嚮導
What?
什麼啊
No wonder they chose Aika.
那怪不得會選小愛
Aika is cute and smart.
小愛又可愛又聰明
High spec? I'm not a computer.
什麼叫高規格 又不是電腦...
She didn't use that term.
學姊她沒有用這種說法啦
But look at the outcome.
但妳看 就結果而言
Luckily, our class chose Sasaki and you, the two top.
好險我們班派出的是 妳跟佐佐木這兩大巨頭
Sajo, is that what you really think?
小佐城你真心這麼想嗎
Huh? What's the matter?
怎麼了嗎
Don't you want to replace Sasaki?
你應該很想取代佐佐木同學吧
Then you can be a guide with Aika.
這樣你就能跟小愛一起當嚮導了
What are you thinking?
你到底是怎麼想的
People like me can't do it.
像我這種人無法啦
I'm not even in any clubs.
我甚至沒參與任何社團活動
But didn't you help Ichinose?
但你不是幫助了一之瀨同學嗎
That came naturally, or you could say I couldn't stand still.
那是...自然而然 又或者該說我無法坐視不管
Are you plotting something?
你是不是對人家意圖不軌啊
I'm not. What's with that look?
我才沒有 妳那眼神是怎樣
I did, however, take the initiative
我為了好好打工
to communicate with her for work purposes.
是有主動跟她交流沒錯啦
After all, pestering is your specialty.
畢竟糾纏不休是你的看家本領嘛
Watch your words.
注意妳的措詞
Don't cause trouble for others.
你不要讓別人帶來困擾喔
I won't.
我才不會
I won't cause trouble for anyone anymore.
我再也不會讓任何人困擾了
Will you come to school again?
你還會來學校嗎
I still need to move the chairs back, and I have other tasks to complete.
我還得收拾東西 也有一些其他文書工作要做
What about you, Kei?
圭妳呢
I'm supposed to be in the club.
我應該就是要一直練球吧
I see.
這樣啊...
Listen.
我說...
Let's gather again.
我們再出來聚聚吧
Let's gather again after the campus open day.
等校園參觀日結束後
No?
好嗎...
I'm totally okay with it.
我...完全沒問題
But I'm not sure when I'll finish the work.
但我這邊不知道什麼時候才會結束
Although the open day schedule is set,
校園參觀日的行程雖然已經安排好了
I have no idea how long the cleaning will take.
但我不知道收拾要花多少時間
It's okay.
沒關係啦
Then I'll gossip about you while I wait for you.
那我就一邊說你壞話一邊等你
Give me the iced tea if you say that.
妳敢說這種話 把我的冰紅茶還來
No way.
我不要
I'll let go if you apologize to me.
妳道歉我就放手
Stop it, you two.
你們兩個別鬧了
Aika.
小愛
BINAN BOOKSTORE
(濱南書店)
Good job, Ichinose. See you tomorrow.
一之瀨同學妳辛苦了 明天見
You're off tomorrow, Sajo.
佐城同學 你明天排休喔
Oh yeah, it's the campus open day tomorrow.
對喔 明天是校園參觀日
Thank you, Ichinose.
謝謝妳 一之瀨同學
I totally forgot about it.
我差點就忘了
You're welcome.
不客氣
Are you certain you'll be fine on your own for the entire day tomorrow?
明天一整天就妳一個人 沒問題嗎
I'll be fine. Thank you, Sajo.
沒問題 佐城同學你也辛苦了
Thank you, I will leave it to you then.
謝謝 那就拜託妳囉
I'll tell Senior Ichinose that you're trustworthy.
我會跟一之瀨學長說妳很可靠
I still have a lot to improve.
我還差得遠了
(Dreaming Boy is a Realist, The)
《滿懷美夢的少年是現實主義者》
The president of Koetsu High School's student union has something to say.
鴻越高中的學生會長有話跟大家說
Everyone, please gather in the gym.
請大家先到體育館集合
The gym is this way.
體育館往這邊走
Hello, everyone.
各位同學好
Welcome to Koetsu High School.
歡迎來到鴻越高中
I'm the student union president, Yuki Hayato.
我是學生會長 結城颯斗
I hope you can learn about
鴻越高中是一所怎樣的學校
Koetsu High School
在校學生又是什麼樣的類型
and its students today.
希望今天能讓大家對此有所瞭解
He deserves to be the student union president.
真不愧是學生會長
He captured the hearts of the female students in an instant.
他立刻就擄獲了在場女學生的芳心
That's the end of my speech, thank you everyone.
我的致詞就到此結束
He really is our school's prince.
真不愧是本校的王子殿下
But our school's princess is smiling at the middle school students.
本校的公主殿下則是 面帶微笑地看著中學生們
And I must be the servant.
而我則是傭人吧
Let me see.
我看看...
You're Inoue, Sasaki, Nakata, and Yamamoto
妳們是來自美白濱國中的
from White Beach Middle School, right?
井上同學 笹木同學 中田同學跟山本同學吧
I'm Sasaki, your guide for today.
我是擔任嚮導的佐佐木
Nice to meet you.
今天就請多多指教了
-Nice to meet you.
-請...請多指教 -麻煩你了
My surname is Sasaki, which sounds similar to Sasaki's but has different characters.
我的姓氏讀音跟笹木同學一樣 但漢字寫法不同呢
I'm Sasaki, with the human character on the left.
我是人字旁加上左字的佐佐木
with the bamboo character on the right.
我是竹字頭的笹木
There's another person who will be guiding you with me.
這是今天的另一位嚮導
I'm Natsukawa, nice to meet you.
我叫夏川 請多指教
Nice to meet you.
請多指教
Next, we will take you around the campus.
接下來我們要帶妳們逛逛校園
Let me ask if you have any questions first.
我先問一下大家有沒有疑問好了
Any questions?
有嗎
I have one. Can I ask a question?
我有 我想問一個問題
Go ahead.
妳說吧
What is the relationship between the two of you?
請問你們兩位是什麼關係
-He's blushing. -Yeah, he is.
-他臉紅了 -對啊
Sasaki and I are just classmates.
我們就只是同班同學
I see.
這樣啊
Then let's go.
那我們出發吧
After this, we won't answer any more personal questions.
之後我們就不再回答這種私人問題囉
Okay.
好的...
I-I'm sorry.
對…對不起
It's okay.
沒關係
Our school has about 630 students.
我們學校大概有630名學生
With six classes per grade and 35 students per class,
每個年級有六班 每班35人
it's easy to remember the names and faces of classmates.
所以很容易記得同學的姓名跟長相
Although our school has a high college admission rate,
雖然升學率很高
some people choose to work or attend vocational schools after graduation.
但也有人會在畢業後馬上就業 或是去唸職業學校
There are also a lot of club activities.
社團活動也相當盛行
So it's the so-called all-round development?
也就是一般所謂的文武雙全
Sasaki, you're very good at explaining.
佐佐木同學你很會講解耶
So are you.
妳也是啊
Maybe it's because we're all the eldest in the family.
可能是因為我們都是家中的老大吧
Is that so?
是嗎...
How's Airi doing recently? I wanted to see her.
小愛莉她最近好嗎 我還想再見見她
Oh, about that…
這個嘛...
Let's talk about it some other time.
下次有機會再說吧
Sorry, I was being presumptuous.
抱歉 是我太唐突了
Can you all keep up?
大家有跟上來嗎
Yes, we can.
有的
Senior Natsukawa, why did you choose Koetsu High School?
夏川學姊妳為什麼選了鴻越高中呢
Because it has a high college admission rate and the most beautiful uniforms.
因為這裡升學率高 制服又最好看吧
I think so too.
我也這麼認為
The uniforms here are really pretty.
這裡的制服很可愛
The school rules are also relatively lax.
而且校規也比較自由
Is White Beach really strict?
美白濱果然很嚴格嗎
If your hair is messy from sleeping, you'll get scolded.
光是早上睡醒頭髮沒整理好就會被罵
So it's the so-called lady's education.
屬於千金小姐的教育方式
That's right.
對吧
But our school also has a student council,
不過我們學校也有風紀委員會
so it might not be much different from yours in this respect.
這方面跟妳們學校可能差不多
You don't need to worry about that.
這點學姊妳大可放心
I really admire the student council president, Senior Shinomiya.
我很崇拜四之宮風紀委員長
That's right, although our school is very free,
沒錯 我們學校雖然自由
it doesn't mean you can do whatever you want.
但並不代表可以放肆
To gain equal freedom, you must first accept responsibility.
學生得承擔責任才能得到對等的自由
Does this imply that there are a lot of honest people?
意思是說有很多耿直的人嗎
I can't be sure, but what you said might be right.
我也說不準...但也許妳說得沒錯
-Next is… -Really?
-接著是... -真的假的啊
Are you already seeing someone?
原來妳已經有對象了啊
You must have kissed already, haven't you?
想必妳一定親過嘴了吧
Did you even go further? When?
不只親嘴吧？什麼時候的事？
That's none of your business.
這與你無關吧
Y-You guys should stop.
你們...適可而止吧
Why don't you tell us about it?
妳就告訴我們嘛
I really want to know.
我好想知道啊
This doesn't look good.
情況有點不妙
What are you guys doing?
你們在幹什麼
This doesn't seem like the regular tour route.
這裡不是正規的參觀路線吧
Natsukawa?
夏川同學...
Aizawa, are you okay?
藍澤同學妳沒事吧？
She's so cute.
她好可愛...
I must attend Koetsu High School.
我一定要進鴻越高中
I don't mind if she is older than me.
年紀比我大我也OK
Wh-What?
怎...怎樣
This school doesn't need people like you.
這所學校並不需要你們這種人
What do you mean by that?
妳說什麼
I mean, we don't need you here.
我說這裡不需要你們
Didn't you hear me?
你們沒聽見嗎
We came here specifically for a school tour.
我們可是特地來參觀校園的耶
No one invited you.
沒人請你們來
You are the ones who want to challenge our entrance exam.
要挑戰入學考試的人是你們
We are just guides.
我們只不過是嚮導
We are not trying to please you.
並不是在討好你們
-Right? -Huh? Yes, that's right.
-對吧 -咦...嗯 沒錯
You can also visit our cultural festival.
妳們也可以來參觀看看我們的校慶
Despite the fact that many schools have recently downsized the event,
雖然最近不少學校都縮小舉辦規模
Koetsu will make it a grand event.
但鴻越會辦得很盛大喔
That sounds great.
好棒喔
I'm looking forward to it as well.
我也很期待
We'll have to come along then.
到時候我們一定要來
Definitely come.
就這麼說定了
Next time, I want Mr. Sajo to be our guide.
希望下次佐城先生能來當我的嚮導
You're talking about that guy, right?
妳是在說那個人吧
Fuka is daydreaming again.
風香又在幻想了
N-No, I'm not daydreaming.
我...才不是幻想
Natsukawa, you can be quite harsh.
原來夏川妳還會那麼嚴厲地教訓人啊
I guess I'm used to dealing with difficult boys.
看來我應該是習慣對付難纏的男生了
That's about it for the campus tour.
校園參觀差不多就到這裡了
If you are interested in enrolling, you can also visit the canteen and clubs.
如果妳們有意願的話 還可以去食堂用餐跟參觀社團
Have you finished your tour?
你們也參觀完了嗎
We are really sorry.
真的很抱歉
We genuinely want to attend this school.
我們真心想進這所學校
We hope you will welcome us when the time comes.
屆時希望學姊妳能多多關照我們
I see. Good luck.
我知道了 你們加油喔
Yes.
好...
Um… Thank you so much for today.
那個...今天非常謝謝學長學姊
Don't mention it. We should thank you.
不客氣 我們才要謝謝妳們
-Wataru. -Mr. Sajo!
-阿涉 -佐城先生
Mr. Sajo!
佐城先生
Miss Sasaki?
這不是笹木小姐嗎
And Sasaki. Natsukawa?
還有佐佐木跟夏川...
What a combination.
這是什麼陣容啊
I have a bad feeling about this.
我有種不祥的預感
I came for a school tour.
我是來參觀校園的
I didn't expect to see you.
沒想到我能在這裡見到你
I see.
原來是這樣啊
We have seniors guiding us on the tour.
有學長學姊帶我們參觀
I see, I see.
原來如此啊...
What a coincidence.
世上竟有如此巧合！
Fuka.
風香
Is this the Mr. Sajo you mentioned?
他就是妳說的那個佐城先生嗎
Which Mr. Sajo?
哪個佐城先生...
Stop teasing me here.
討厭 不要在這裡捉弄我了
Are you the Mr. Sajo
你就是讓不善言詞的小風香
who taught Fuka how to speak politely?
學會禮貌用語的那個佐城先生嗎
Are you the Mr. Sajo who made Fuka
你就是讓沉迷在少女漫畫世界的風香
realize the futility of her romance manga obsession?
體會到現實的那個佐城先生嗎
Are you the Mr. Sajo who taught
你就是讓超級少根筋的風香
super naive Fuka some common sense?
懂得常識的那個佐城先生嗎
W-Which Mr. Sajo?
哪個佐城先生...
No, no. I'm not obsessed.
不對 我才沒有沉迷呢
And I'm not super naive.
我也沒有少一根筋好嗎
Strange. Is Miss Sasaki always like this?
奇怪 笹木小姐原來是這樣的人嗎
With me and Ichinose, she's different. It appears she has become more naive.
她跟我和一之瀨同學在一起時不一樣 好像變得天真無邪...
Senior Sajo.
佐城學長
Please take care of Fuka.
風香她就拜託你了喔
Even though she's a bit strange, she's a good kid.
雖然她有點怪怪的 但她是個好孩子
It's too late for you guys to say this.
妳們現在說這些太晚了啦
My bond with Mr. Sajo is already strong.
我跟佐城先生交情匪淺
He's gentle, knowledgeable, and polite.
他又溫柔又博學又有禮貌
Like the time we went out together, he…
像我們之前一起出去時 他也...
Hold on, Miss Sasaki.
等等 妳在說什麼...
I-I-I didn't mean that.
啊...我不是那個意思...
Well, we should leave now.
那...我們該告辭了
Fuka?
小風香...
We've really troubled you today.
不好意思打擾了
-Let's call it a day, guys. -What's going on?
-我們今天就先告辭了 -什麼啊
Wait for me!
妳們等等我啦
They are, after all, a group of middle school students.
她們果然還是一群國中生啊
Yes.
是啊
Sajo, hang in there.
佐城 你加油啊
Sasaki!
佐佐木
Um…
呃 那個...
Hello, Natsukawa.
夏川同學妳好...
What are you doing?
幹嘛
No, it's nothing.
不 沒什麼
Come over here.
你過來
They're talking about Sajo?
她說小佐城...
Gentle and knowledgeable, what else?
又溫柔又博學 還有什麼來著
Polite.
有禮貌
Polite, huh? What else?
有禮貌啊 還有咧
-Going out together. -Yes, yes. Going out together.
-一起出去 -對對 一起出去
You say you're busy all the time,
你嘴上說你很忙
but you seem to have a lot of fun and enjoy it.
但你好像經歷豐富又樂在其中嘛
I'm not enjoy it.
我可沒有樂在其中
I do have a lot of fun…
經歷豐富倒是沒錯...
What do you mean by that?
經歷豐富是指？
Don't ask such a tactless question.
妳別問這種蠢問題
My swimsuit photo.
我的泳裝照...
I confess.
我全招就是了
So that's how it is.
原來如此啊
Alright, give me your phone.
好了 把你的手機給我
Why? I've confessed everything.
為什麼啊 我都一五一十地招了
That's a different matter.
那是兩碼子事
I'll be shy.
我很難為情
I won't bury it in a folder.
我不會讓照片埋沒在資料夾裡
I will admire it regularly.
我會定期瞻仰的
That's why I'm not happy about it.
所以我才不樂意啊
Sajo, you are very honest in such situations.
小佐城你這時候就特別誠實呢
See, even Ashida says so.
妳看 蘆田都這麼說了
Idiot.
笨蛋...
Then you should come and play with us.
那你倒是也跟我們一起玩啊...
If you don't want to, it's okay.
你不願意就算了
Wait, wait! I didn't hear just now.
等等 我沒聽到妳說什麼
I really didn't hear it, please say it again.
真的啦 拜託妳再說一次
You should come and play with us.
你倒是也跟我們一起玩啊...
Me? Play with you?
妳要我...跟妳們一起玩...
Y-Yes.
嗯...對啊
Since you have time to play with others,
既然你有時間跟別人出去玩
you can play with us too.
那也可以跟我們一起玩吧
You don't want to?
你不想嗎
Of course not! I'm very grateful.
在下很樂意 萬分感激
Why have you become a samurai?
你幹嘛一副武士樣
WHERE ARE WE GOING TO PLAY?
(我們要去哪玩？)
SINCE I'M BRINGING ALONG AIRI, THE PLACES WE CAN CHOOSE ARE LIMITED
(我要帶著愛莉 能去的地方有限)
OH, NATSUKAWA'S LITTLE SISTER?
(噢 夏川的妹妹！)
WHY NOT GO TO THE BEACH AGAIN?
(要再去海邊嗎？)
NICE
(nice)
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE GOING TO THE BEACH WITH THIS LINEUP
(這個陣容去海邊不好吧)
HEHE, AFTER ALL, WE HAVE TO WEAR SWIMSUITS
(嘻嘻 畢竟要穿泳裝)
THAT'S A LETDOWN
(洩氣)
WHY NOT COME TO MY HOUSE?
(要來我家嗎？)
THAT SOUNDS GOOD
(不錯哦！)
IT WON'T BE A BURDEN ON AIRI EITHER
(這樣愛莉也輕鬆)
YAY!
(好耶！)
SAJO, ARE YOU STILL ALIVE?
(小佐城你還活著嗎？)
I'M STILL ALIVE
(我還活著)
I DIDN'T FORCE YOU TO COME
(你不想來也沒關係啦)
I WANT TO GGO!
(我要許！)
I WANT TO GOO!
(我要趣！)
I WANT TO GO!
(我要去！)
CALM DOWN
(你冷靜點)
YES!
(是！)
DON'T SAY ANYTHING WEIRD TO AIRI
(你不要對愛莉說奇怪的話哦)
OF COURSE!
(我當然不會！)
DON'T MAKE JOKES THAT CHILDREN WON'T UNDERSTAND
(你不准說小孩不懂的玩笑話)
MAKE SURE TO DRESS NEATLY BEFORE COMING
(你記得穿著整潔再來)
REMEMBER TO GREET I DON'T LIKE RUDE PEOPLE
(你要記得打招呼 我不喜歡沒禮貌的人)
AIKA, ENOUGH
(小愛 差不多夠了)
IF IT'S JUST US, IT'S FINE. BUT IT'S DIFFERENT WITH AIRI.
(要是只有我就算了 但愛莉也在)
AT YOUR SERVICE!
(悉聽尊便！)
THANKS FOR INVITING
(萬事拜託)
REALLY
(真是的)
Aika, you…
我說小愛妳啊...
What's up?
怎麼了嗎
Although I understand your feelings,
雖然我瞭解妳的心情
I believe you should be gentler with Sajo.
但妳還是別對小佐城太兇喔
Otherwise, the distance between you two will only get further.
要不然你們的距離又會越來越遠
I wish you both happiness.
我希望你們兩個都能幸福
What's wrong with you, sister?
姊姊妳怎麼了